Gary Young: Hey.
David Mendenhall: Hey, Gary.
Gary Young: How you doing?
David Mendenhall: Tired.
Gary Young: But you are back home?
David Mendenhall: Yep, in one of my homes.
Gary Young: Huh.
Gary Young: You have more than one home.
David Mendenhall: No, we're moving, but we haven't moved.
Gary Young: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Hey, Wade.
Wade Brown: Hello!
David Mendenhall: So are you, all set up for Monday?
Wade Brown: Hmm… Monday?
David Mendenhall: They don't even tell you these things.
Wade Brown: No?
Wade Brown: I have filled out the 100 forms or so that they have, and then they sent me another email after saying I was done, saying, oh, you have another 100 to do, so I'll do those in the morning.
David Mendenhall: Okay, so you're not all set. The guys are, they're on vacation until the 24th.
David Mendenhall: So, I would just use next week to, like, make sure all your…
David Mendenhall: VPN and shit is taken care of.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I mean, it's just… I'll fire off an email, bill an hour or two for it, whatever.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Just 80 hours, right? Like, not a whole lot.
David Mendenhall: Hey, Thomas.
Wade Brown: Some pizza and beer money.
David Mendenhall: We're all here.
Wade Brown: I spent it on my new 3D printer.
David Mendenhall: You got a 3D printer?
Wade Brown: I bought a Voron kit, and I've just been grinding away on it for the past 2 weeks, one of those assembly
Wade Brown: For 40 hours plus.
Kostadis Roussos: from my house.
Wade Brown: I don't see any dicks.
Wade Brown: Are you sure you're in Santorini?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, sorry. Just ignore it, just ignore it.
David Mendenhall: You're not on headphones, Kostadis?
Kostadis Roussos: No, not yet, because everybody's asleep.
Wade Brown: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Just don't… the jokes can be kept to a minimum, just to a minimum today.
Wade Brown: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: Just today. Just today. Actually, you could go with the dick jokes. This is Greece. They probably won't notice. I'm… I'm…
Gary Young: Stephane, I approve of your shirt.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: What does this shirt say?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, it's…
Gary Young: I don't know. Like, it looks really appropriate.
David Mendenhall: The good barbarian shirt.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: It's actually a summer.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Horai.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah, right, it is.
Wade Brown: Oh, from, like, Ninja Scrolls or something.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Excellent.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It could be a samurai, a barbarian samurai, who knows?
Gary Young: Who knows?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It doesn't sound right when you say it, but… Anyway.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me just, get… let me just, get… okay, so let me just bring up the summary so I can remind myself. I don't know whether the rest of you remembered what happened last week.
Kostadis Roussos: But I just woke up, so it doesn't hurt for me to remind myself.
Kostadis Roussos: Thanks.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. Yes, I don't know what's going on. Okay, so there were a bunch of things you guys wanted to do, so…
Wade Brown: I need to get my turtle soup.
David Mendenhall: I picked a name for the band.
Kostadis Roussos: You did?
David Mendenhall: Lathander's death.
Gary Young: Well, then…
Kostadis Roussos: Here's.
David Mendenhall: Death.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: F.
Gary Young: Death. Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Controversial.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, see.
David Mendenhall: The death battle ban, Lathander's death.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Couldn't possibly have any other meanings.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, where we left our part… where we left our party off, they had a dinner with the Lord Protector to prepare for, a dawn performance, the spire of the Morninglord to deliver, a private meeting…
Kostadis Roussos: with Lord Cassian's residence to arrange, and a growing mystery surrounding a dead noblewoman, a missing gnome, and a broken interplanar shipping device.
Kostadis Roussos: Their next stop would be the Counting House, where a letter of recommendation waited to open doors into the disrupted supply chain of the Lionshield Coster. Never winter, it seemed, was never going to let them rest. Alright, so the plan was to start with the Lionshield Coster, if I recall correctly.
David Mendenhall: The counting house?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, the count… yes, the counting house.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sort out some supply chain issues, or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so just to remind you what happened,
Kostadis Roussos: Just to remind, folks,
Kostadis Roussos: Linene, who… Graywind was, had a…
Kostadis Roussos: I guess it would be a franchise, that's what we'd call it, the world.
Kostadis Roussos: of Lionshield Coster, Koster. Now, just to be clear, it's not a franchise, you know, it's part of a merchant guild. That's what we call it these days. And so, she was being… what you learned was that she was being supplied by…
Kostadis Roussos: Some kind of interplanar dimension device that reduced costs of shipping goods to practically zero.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: But…
Kostadis Roussos: Until it stopped working, and now she's been reduced to doing things the old-fashioned way, and moving goods around.
Kostadis Roussos: And, there was a… and so…
David Mendenhall: What is…
Kostadis Roussos: What a shame. What a shame.
Kostadis Roussos: And, she suggested to Brewbarry that, you know, perhaps he could go to the counting house to find out, you know, whether there's anything that could be done about the supply chain issues.
Kostadis Roussos: and whether there was a way to move supplies, etc, etc. So that was the intent of going to the counting house, which is to find, like, how exactly will I move my…
Kostadis Roussos: Soft, cuddly.
Kostadis Roussos: Adorable.
Kostadis Roussos: bathrooms.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Utgartian barbarians used to be all about, you know, this hack and the slash and the violence and the whatnot. Brewbarry wants to make it about the soft bathrobe.
Wade Brown: He won't.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, I mean, everybody needs a break, you know, in life.
David Mendenhall: Self-care.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What's the best way to take a break than to, you know, put on your soft bathrobe, just chill and relax?
Kostadis Roussos: Chill and relax, right? Especially when it's over your…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of course, yes, I've been diagnosed.
David Mendenhall: Do you ever go into battle with the bathrobe?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I was gonna ask, is the bathrobe over or under the dragon scale armor?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Man, it could be a concept, but then you'd risk, you know, staining it with blood and shit, so… probably not.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, it's…
David Mendenhall: All right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Over the downtimes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sorry?
Kostadis Roussos: That's true.
David Mendenhall: Well, you could always wash it, right?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, barbarians don't wash their clothes now. I'm not familiar with that concept.
David Mendenhall: It's a revelation.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, that's… we're not familiar with that concept.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You don't have to explain this.
David Mendenhall: You could use Mending.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: As long as you do it while I'm not watching.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What good is it to wash, you know, your barbarian clothes when you're gonna get them dirty in the next, you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Few hours, or days, or minutes, or whatever.
Gary Young: Few hours, that sounds right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, there's no point. Just no point. Just, you know, keep it as it is. Plus, you know, you call it dirt, I call it sweat and blood, you know, that's… that's what we barbarians live for.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Not on your bathroom. Got it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Just not on the bathrobe, absolutely.
David Mendenhall: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I presume you arrive at the counting house. As you arrive at the counting house, Vukradin, of course, is very excited, because he has the, let… he has a con… he has this confront-free letter of credit, don't forget, that he acquired from
Kostadis Roussos: From his mine payout.
David Mendenhall: Brewbarry, right?
Kostadis Roussos: No, I thought you also had the letter of credit. That's something I…
David Mendenhall: I have a lot of credit.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, let me just make sure.
David Mendenhall: The mine paid something?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me just make sure I got it right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Who would have thought, you know, gold mining bizarre.
David Mendenhall: I don't think we got that.
David Mendenhall: I guess we didn't go down that path, sorry.
David Mendenhall: We turned to page 72, not to page 13.
Wade Brown: Doesn't that sound super familiar?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I have a letter of introduction to the Counting House that Linene gave me.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I guess the letter of credit is for later, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: We won'.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We don't need it, because we're gonna be, you know, filthy rich from all the donations that we're gonna collect in Neverwinter, so…
Kostadis Roussos: Just make sure.
David Mendenhall: You mean the… the charitable foundation will be filthy Rush?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, yes Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's exactly what I mean.
David Mendenhall: That's exactly what you meant.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm giving one more second, let me just… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Michael…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So I walk into the counting house.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, she walked me back.
David Mendenhall: Who do we meet?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: booming voice, and I say, Hello, good folks, I am Brewbarry Rootsmasher, Ogolo… no, sorry. OG… Ogonakanu. Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, oh, okay, yes, now I remember what happened. Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I bring here a letter of introduction from Linene, and I've heard that you're having some trouble with the supply chain, and…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Something that maybe I can help with.
David Mendenhall: Who are you talking.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, hold on just a second.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: There's nobody.
David Mendenhall: I hear a Brewbarry.
Kostadis Roussos: Really?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Damn! I had prepared that speech in my bathrobe last night.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I rehearsed it for, like, 15.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, so what…
David Mendenhall: It was a good one. You know, if you want, I can give you some tips on how to be more persuasive. I've got a silvery tongue.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: which I do not have. My, my axe is my tongue, or my…
David Mendenhall: Well, you… What a good speech, it was, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so, zip.
David Mendenhall: You need to remember to wait for people to enter the room, and then you start.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, where are they? Where is everyone?
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So you walk into,
Kostadis Roussos: you walk into it inside, the counting house is, you know, it's a typical medieval bank for a fire… for a high-end industrial.
Kostadis Roussos: For high-end industrialists, you walk in, there's a lot of tables, and someone notices you and says, hello, hello, my name is Oral
Kostadis Roussos: My name is Oral B. Vance. How can I help you?
David Mendenhall: Oral B. Vance?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Did I get that right? Oral B. Vance?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sounds like some space-based brand.
Wade Brown: Some weird pun that we're missing.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry. Sorry, Andrell Vance. Andrell Vance, sorry.
Wade Brown: Sounds a little…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Better. I'm true. Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, I have Drail.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I just told you.
Kostadis Roussos: I agree, but it goes, hold on.
David Mendenhall: Okay, alright, this is Brewbarry's moment. Go for it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: This is your… this is your lucky day, Aurelan.
Kostadis Roussos: Why?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: My halberd and my friends here are here to sort out your supply chain problems.
Kostadis Roussos: We don't have a supply chain problem.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Aha, have I been lied to, then? Here's a letter of introduction by, Linene, whatever her name is. She's my wealth management.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Consultant?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And she told me she couldn't move around my bathrobes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Because…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, oh, what are you making again?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr. Brewbarry, first of all, I think your costume is wonderful, and I really admire the cosplaying of it, but is it…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now, slippery slope here, Aurelan.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Use your next words very carefully.
David Mendenhall: I have a question.
Kostadis Roussos: I recall?
David Mendenhall: What do you count?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, this is accounting.
Kostadis Roussos: The, the, the leaf…
Wade Brown: -Oh.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Mr. Vukradin? Vukradin?
David Mendenhall: Yes, I am Vukradin, and we are Lathander's Death.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, I… I… I don't know what that… that's…
David Mendenhall: It's our band, Lathander's Death.
Kostadis Roussos: But yes, but Mr. Vukradin, I was speaking to Ms… I was speaking to,
David Mendenhall: Yes, but I had a question.
David Mendenhall: And you didn't answer my…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Let's not get sidetracked here.
David Mendenhall: I was.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but… but I'm doing business with Mr.
Kostadis Roussos: My pleasure.
David Mendenhall: It's fair when I can ask my question.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, one moment. I do have a piece of paper for you too, Mr. Vukradin, and I'm really delighted that you came by. But let me help Mr. Brewbarry first, if that would be okay with you.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're not gonna help me, I'm gonna help you, old man. Don't get, you know, things confused in your little… that little head of yours.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now, please tell me, is there some business to be done here, or should I go elsewhere?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, what are you making?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What do you mean, what am I baking?
Kostadis Roussos: Well.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Am I supposed to tell you what I'm making? I've got this letter here.
Kostadis Roussos: See, this, this, this letter of… this is a letter of…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, well, so what the letter says is that, you are… that Linene is saying that she wants us to lend her money so that she can start her business, but she doesn't describe the nature of the business.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm, I'm gonna bloom…
Gary Young: Do you love it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: to the world, you know, how cruel this world.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: is, and I'm giving this roughness to all…
Kostadis Roussos: All the people.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: all the good people of the Forgotten Realms by, providing them with, supplying them with bathrobes.
Kostadis Roussos: That's very interesting. He takes a little piece of paper quill, and starts scribbling some notes down. Do you know how much this will cost to make?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I have absolutely no idea, which is why I have a wealth management consultant. I suggest that you talk to her.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, very well. I will make a note of talking to her. And how do you intend to ship your goods?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What do I look like? Some merchant? You know, the logistics, guy? No.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I app and slash.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, excuse me.
David Mendenhall: with an idea.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What do you want me to do here?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, dude.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Good job.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, oh, I see you intend to use LionShield Coster as your shipping agent and business arrangement. Oh, yes, of course, how silly of me. Mrs. Linene here points out…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Finally, you're starting to think.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, Chop Chop, let's get this going, please.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I'm sorry, he could pause this. He goes, Mr. Brewbarry, I wish to apologize. I want you to know that I have no objection to Lionshield Coster's business, or their interest in… and I've done wonderful business with them, but their rights have gone ridiculously up, and I'm afraid that, based on my calculations, and he pulls out, like, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, he pulls out some calculations that you can't read.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So what, a few seconds ago, he didn't know what I was making, and now he has… Hugely.
David Mendenhall: Counted.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: stations?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, it's… you don't know what he has, you can't read. I mean, if somebody else wants to read it, it's…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Are you sure his name is not Texas Instrument? No, he can count pretty fast.
Wade Brown: There's a dated reference.
David Mendenhall: Just call them techs from now on.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, sorry, he presents a small piece of paper, right? So he scribbles it down, he says, well, I will have to double-check the numbers, but unfortunately, I have to be honest with you, with the margins we expect, even with Margaster's very generous margins and prices, and the cost of moving goods in and out of Phandalin, plus… and he starts going, I don't think… I feel that the county behind.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Sorry, let me, let me, let me cut you off. You know, yadda yadda yadda yadda, you get my blood pumping. Just, just tell me you're gonna get it done, and that's it. Otherwise, I'm gonna get upset.
Gary Young: You're not, you're not telling Ann.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Don't you see me upset.
Gary Young: We're not tallying in two additional factors.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: The temple markup?
Gary Young: and the Churchill with Anders, bulk, demand.
David Mendenhall: And the band.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, goes,
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you are one of the blessed of Lathander.
Kostadis Roussos: Then he pauses and goes, and you're a drow.
David Mendenhall: We're within our staff.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're very perceptive. Aurelan.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, but Mr. Brewbarry, I wish to inform you that I do have a solution to your problem.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's what I want to hear.
Kostadis Roussos: You wouldn't let me… I realize this is very agitated, and I realize you've already made business arrangements with… you've already made some early business arrangements with Lionshield Coster's agent, Linene Graywind, but since your business is in production, what I would suggest you do is, instead of using Lionshield Coster for distribution of goods, you reach out to House Margaster. They're the ones who have managed to reduce the pricing of goods
Kostadis Roussos: quite significantly, and I believe with their margins and their arrangements, you would be able to run the business most efficiently. And if you could secure a letter of, agreement with them.
David Mendenhall: Oh my goodness.
Kostadis Roussos: a letter of agreement with them. We would be more than delighted to sign on the dotted line.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do I look like a fool?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Tell me.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr… Mr. Brewbarry.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do I look like a fool, Aurelan?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, and I take my… I stopped…
David Mendenhall: SmartCast.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Pulling my halberd and just, you know, tapping it in my other hand.
Kostadis Roussos: No, but… he looks…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, so, no, exactly. So, what did I tell you? Who is Linux?
Kostadis Roussos: I… she is your wealth advisor. I'm not saying…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly. And you tell me to go and do some business with somebody else.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, Mr. Brilliant.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You think I'm an idiot? Did you have, like, some sweet deal with this other guy? I didn't give two shit about it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now, I told you, I have a wealth management consultant, she has a supply company, she's gonna borrow money from you, you're gonna lend it to her, and you're gonna get this done.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Surely, surely there's an interest rate…
David Mendenhall: that you would find acceptable, given the increased risk of, you know, a lower margin distributor. We can come to some sort of arrangement there, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Finn a bit strange.
David Mendenhall: No, I got a 17. Take 17.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah. I also find it a bit strange that she had this technique to get her, you know, prices down for supplying things, and then suddenly she tells me, you know, that she's got some supply chain issue that I should talk to you about.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You tell me you don't know about it, and then you point me to this other guy who has found a way to magically get his cost.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, Mr. Brewbarry, and Mr. Vukradin, I think your concerns are legitimate, but I… I would be remiss, I would be remiss as… look, if what you wish to do is to borrow.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: How remiss you're gonna be if you continue down this path, my friend.
Kostadis Roussos: Is it not?
David Mendenhall: You keep talking, you need to, you need to stun.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: doing… doing stuff. You know, stop talking to me, go do what you gotta do.
Kostadis Roussos: You see, so, so, hold on, Mr. Brewbarry, I felt as, as your banker.
Kostadis Roussos: It was my duty.
Kostadis Roussos: to offer you a better path. But if you wish to do business with the Lionshield Coster.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Are you, are you my wealth management consultant?
Kostadis Roussos: Mr. I, you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Are you? No, you're the money man. So what you're gonna do is give us money so that we can do business.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, very well, Mr. Well, Mr. Brewbarry.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's what I want to hear.
Kostadis Roussos: As usual…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You want to be my friend, Aurelan.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he goes… he's… Meanwhile, there's a little bit of a crowd looking at you.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, you, you kind of… you… there's…
Kostadis Roussos: There's a… there's a… there's a bit of… there's a bit of a crowd surrounding you at this point in time, and
Kostadis Roussos: he signs the paperwork. He gives you the paperwork for the loan. So you've decided… so he gives you the paperwork for the loan, which is…
Kostadis Roussos: quite significant, but we'll be able to kickstart your business with… Linene will be able to kickstart your sheep business.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So now, now, let's go back to the topic of supply chain issues. Are you sure you don't know anything about it? Because she told me you would.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, oh, so, she… well…
Kostadis Roussos: Unfortunately, all I know is that there was some kind of system that Lionshield Coster was using
Kostadis Roussos: that stopped working some time ago for reasons that are obscure and apologetic, but I do not… you'd have to go consult House Margaster if you wanted to learn more. I personally just know that as a result of this sudden change in their shipping methods, the prices of goods shipped by Lionshield Coster has gone up considerably, and their business.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: This is how you do business, you know?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You send people left and right? No, no. So you're gonna go to a house like Astra, you're gonna find out what's going on, and I'm gonna come back tomorrow, and you're gonna tell me
Stéphane Bourdeaud: how I can fix it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You get it, Aurelan.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're gonna… money that I'm gonna give you.
Kostadis Roussos: So just as a timeout, you do have a lead at what else might be broken, so I just want to make sure, like… I'm… Brewbarry, I just want the rest of the… Brewbarry, I love your…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We've got other things to do. We've got, you know, a list of quests to do in Neverwinter, long like my halberd.
Kostadis Roussos: One of them is actually a lead… one of them is actually a lead on House Margaster.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. Yeah, one of them is the.
David Mendenhall: They're evil.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Evil. No. Okay.
Wade Brown: Were they Cambians?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Anyways, but we probably don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Stephane, just out of character for a moment. House Margaster was a recurring villain in… is a recurring villain in these campaigns, so…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Says…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: They are Moriarty, you mean?
Gary Young: Moriarty, yeah. Okay.
David Mendenhall: Moriarty.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I already had it.
David Mendenhall: Moriarty had class, though.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, they don't? No.
Kostadis Roussos: Just to be clear, they are recur… they are, they are recurring.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Anyway, it doesn't hurt to get multiple angles, so you're gonna… you're gonna go to… to those… this house, and you're gonna find out… Yes, you are.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: I was about to say yes. I was about to say yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: and talk.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're gonna do it?
Kostadis Roussos: And I've got.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're gonna come back, and you're gonna give me what I need.
Kostadis Roussos: Absolutely, mister.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Good job.
David Mendenhall: I'd like you to roll intimidation, I just want to know what you get. Shits and giggles.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: intimidation.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Interesting.
Wade Brown: There you go, like… Helm, or whatever.
David Mendenhall: Alright, decent.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Decent, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, I'm glad I know what that number is.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, do I really need to roll? I mean, you know, I tower over this little guy who probably, his most exciting day in his life was when he went on a.
David Mendenhall: Clearly has advantage, right? Clearly.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You bet.
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, he goes, well, Mr. Rieber, I intend to find out what I can by tomorrow. I… you can rely… you can rely on the Counting House.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm a barbarian, I don't know much about business, but when, you know, when something… When some wheel.
Kostadis Roussos: That's, okay, at this point in time.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You turn, you oil it. That's what we're doing.
Kostadis Roussos: At this point in time… hold on. At this point in time, you see some, like.
Kostadis Roussos: client of the counting house, who kind of sort of looks dressed like you, but, like, whereas you've got, like, real barbarian high.
Wade Brown: Cheap cosplay!
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's worse than that. It's frofy cosplay.
Wade Brown: Oh, jeez.
Wade Brown: Are they mocking him?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, he's, like, this is, you know, some very wealthy dude who's decided to, you know, wear…
Kostadis Roussos: Gergarian barbarian clothes, but instead of being made from hides, it's made from silks, you know, that kind of thing.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: And he walks up to you, and he goes, what a genuine costume!
Kostadis Roussos: Because…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Are you touching my clothes? Be careful.
Kostadis Roussos: Wow, you are… you are really into the bit. I am very impressed.
Kostadis Roussos: And then he tries to mimic you, it's very awkward for a moment there.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I just… I just ignore him.
Kostadis Roussos: So yes, you have, so you, you, yes, you, okay, so you'll come back tomorrow to see what,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We can find out. And in the meantime, we can go on about other business.
David Mendenhall: Can I ask?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: I didn't find out what they count.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Money.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: How?
Kostadis Roussos: Whoa.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, we, we, we, the counting house is a bank.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, and Mr.
David Mendenhall: I could… okay.
Kostadis Roussos: What, yes?
David Mendenhall: Oh, you could have just said you're a bank. Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, we count money.
Gary Young: I thought they count notes or count beats in a measure.
David Mendenhall: They didn't specify.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah.
Gary Young: It's a…
Wade Brown: mystery.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, the… but meanwhile, so the ordeal, after being… after that ordeal,
Wade Brown: Shit.
Kostadis Roussos: turns to Vukradin and says, Mr. Vukradin, there appears to be a, notice of credit.
Kostadis Roussos: for you.
Kostadis Roussos: From the Neverwinter Commission, from the Mountain's Toe Mine.
Gary Young: Yep.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yes!
David Mendenhall: The mine.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, but you'll have to go collect it from those two From that table over there.
David Mendenhall: Okay…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And there, again, you're doing it, Aurelan, and, you know, pointing people left and right instead of doing it yourself. Why don't you go.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, then…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: my friend.
Kostadis Roussos: But because this is unfortunately a different department, Mr. Brewbarry, I do loans, they do fulfillment.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You see my halberd, you see my Axe, there are two different departments as well, you know, and you're about to.
Kostadis Roussos: Meet them.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: both.
David Mendenhall: Brewbarry, Brewbarry, he's not our servant. He's not a slave.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: He's the… he's… he's the banker, we're in a bank.
David Mendenhall: He's a bad banker. He's not good at his job, I'll give you that.
David Mendenhall: But he's not a slave, and we can't order him around.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, he looks… Mr. Vukradin, I want to thank you. Mr. Brewbarry, I wish you to know that you have this… the Counting House's full financial support and backing going forward, but I really, unfortunately, cannot supply this information. Mr. Vukradin, I'm happy to walk you over and make the introduction.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes.
David Mendenhall: I'm… I'm for it.
Gary Young: I have a Chinese wall between departments.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
David Mendenhall: Chinese one, what would the term actually be?
David Mendenhall: A…
David Mendenhall: Hmm… An interdimensional wall. A planar barrier?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, I'm no businessman, but if I have some advice to give you, you know, you gotta think differently. Like, you know…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's not my problem, it's somebody else's is over there, go talk to him. That doesn't work.
Gary Young: It was, like, a…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Trust me.
Gary Young: Firewall, or a wall of fire?
David Mendenhall: Wall of fire, planar barrier… Firewall, wall of fire.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you arrive at the table, and to your surprise, or horror.
Kostadis Roussos: You see the same comedy routine from the Falcon's… Falcon's Lodge.
David Mendenhall: Oh, oh, it's,
Wade Brown: those guys.
David Mendenhall: It's our friends. We have a letter for them.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. And…
David Mendenhall: They're working at the bank?
Kostadis Roussos: Apparently, yes. And it says…
David Mendenhall: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: It's a queue, it's a small folding table with a velvet rope and a queue of zero purple, which says, Rimardo and Mr. Corrin, Divine Accountants and Occasional entertainers.
Wade Brown: Very exciting.
David Mendenhall: I mean, accounting now, wow, they've really sunk low. Jeez.
David Mendenhall: Oh, hey guys!
David Mendenhall: We know you. We have a letter for you! We were actually looking for you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. The, the, the, the Rimardo looks at you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we've been waiting for you for some time. He pulls up his, he pulls up the paper, and he looks through a book, he starts flipping through it, and then he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Pauses.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm here to audit your moral economi- your moral economy.
Kostadis Roussos: All of a sudden, Corin starts producing receipts from every place you've ever been, like, handing them out.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, God.
Wade Brown: He literally brought receipts.
Kostadis Roussos: Right. Amen.
David Mendenhall: Permissible.
Gary Young: We're onsan as well.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, not from.
David Mendenhall: for me.
Kostadis Roussos: Finally, Rimardo picks up one of the papers and looks at it.
Kostadis Roussos: You've… you have not refused dirty money. You have merely laundered it through paperwork with better penmanship.
Kostadis Roussos: And you notice he's staring at the UBT.
David Mendenhall: It was drunk money.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: Who's dirty money?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you what he's, he's,
Kostadis Roussos: And then you also notice that CORN has produced the subcommittee charter, from… that was produced… that was just produced.
Kostadis Roussos: Finally, Corrin looks… Rimardo looks at it, looks at you, and says, well, do you have anything to say?
David Mendenhall: I've got this letter for you from the Falcon, so…
David Mendenhall: Here you go. And, something about a mine?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, he looks at it.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, he says… Corrin, he looks at Corrin, Corrin shrugs, pulls out a stamp, and stamps the ledger with the UBT with comedically
Kostadis Roussos: Comedically… comedically compliant.
David Mendenhall: EBT is comedically compliant. Great.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. It's comedically compliant.
Kostadis Roussos: And then they take your receipt, stamp it again, this time it says approved, and then they just get up and leave.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What the hell was that?
Wade Brown: These guys are weird.
David Mendenhall: Okay, I'm so glad that we ran into them.
David Mendenhall: Are we done counting?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes, you can now go collect your money.
David Mendenhall: What money?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: The receipt, the credit receipt.
Kostadis Roussos: You look at the letter, and it's actually for 200 gold pieces from the Neverwinter Commission.
Kostadis Roussos: For the two… for the mine.
David Mendenhall: 200 gold pieces.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What are mine.
Kostadis Roussos: But the mind.
David Mendenhall: Is it low?
David Mendenhall: It's a loan. It's a letter…
Kostadis Roussos: No, it's… no, it's… it's a… it's a… the letter of credit was so that you could redeem the 200 gold pieces.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Gary Young: Oh, right.
David Mendenhall: Why am I getting… I don't understand, why are they paying me 200 gold.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Proverbs.
Gary Young: mine that we own.
Kostadis Roussos: Remember, the Neverwinter Commission?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Some gold from us, yeah?
Kostadis Roussos: Neverwinter Commission owns the mine.
David Mendenhall: Okay…
Kostadis Roussos: What's his name? Bon Joan was simply an agent…
Wade Brown: Marco, yeah.
David Mendenhall: Oh, somehow I did not know that. So we don't own.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, don't…
David Mendenhall: That's what you'.
Kostadis Roussos: No, yeah, you own a share in the mine that is owned by the.
David Mendenhall: care of the mine. I thought we were the owners, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, you were…
David Mendenhall: session.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you, you, the Falcon and Don Juan.
David Mendenhall: So the $200 is a dividend, or we're selling our shares?
Kostadis Roussos: It's a dividend.
David Mendenhall: It's a dividend.
David Mendenhall: Do we agree that this is fair trade gold?
Gary Young: Yeah, so…
David Mendenhall: Right, we are.
Gary Young: The mine, and therefore the mind's…
Wade Brown: Mine wasn't… yeah, it wasn't ill-gotten treasure, it was pulled from the earth.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yep.
Wade Brown: There's, there's no rifle.
David Mendenhall: to it.
Gary Young: Our shares are something we received in response, you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What do you mean? We cleaned up the mine, we resumed business there.
Kostadis Roussos: We set them up with…
Wade Brown: cheese…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah. Yeah, but… We've done some work here. We deserve.
David Mendenhall: We're not the ones who put it in the ground.
David Mendenhall: I just happened to take it out of the ground.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, you're taking it too.
Wade Brown: Wait, wait, wait, so if you eat a potato, is that an ill-gotten potato because it came out of the ground? Like…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I just have to…
Wade Brown: Understand.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, and you earn money by singing. Who gave you your… So just to be clear.
Kostadis Roussos: Just to be clear, it is a legitimate free trade arrangement, because you did it legally above board, there was no coercion involved.
David Mendenhall: Well, treasure is legal, too.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but this was a proper business.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm just telling you, like, based on the…
Gary Young: Peyton.
Kostadis Roussos: That was your reasoning before, David. I'm just gonna go with that.
Gary Young: The employees were paid.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Wade Brown: cheese.
Gary Young: performed work That work resulted in goods?
David Mendenhall: All right.
Wade Brown: Solve the labor dispute that got them to work, you know?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, that's not…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: If it's not honest money, then you have to tell me what is, because I don't know.
David Mendenhall: labor.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Labor… we did put labor in.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Get this business rolling.
Gary Young: Management labor.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, we put on a lot.
Wade Brown: Hardest and most valuable type of labor.
David Mendenhall: Management? Yes.
David Mendenhall: Hmm.
Gary Young: Okay, I guess that's control, and then our…
David Mendenhall: like, the bourgeois own the means of production. Alright. I will let Gary record the entry.
Gary Young: I'm recording it as Fair Trade Gold.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We could give… we could give some of it to charity that, you know…
David Mendenhall: Sure!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It makes you happy.
David Mendenhall: Your share?
Wade Brown: You're sharing.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm gonna… I'm gonna roll in gold with my bathrobe business anyway.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, Aurelan and Linene are gonna make me rich, so…
Wade Brown: What I'm hearing is if you don't assemble the bathrobes yourself.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. So, yes, alright, alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I heard something about an evil house. Is that where we should go next?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Find out what.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: practices with them.
David Mendenhall: I thought we were doing a performance at the church.
Gary Young: That's at dawn of whatever the next appropriate day is.
David Mendenhall: Okay, and what time is it right now?
Kostadis Roussos: It was the end of the day, so we can start the next day, if you want to… unless you want to do…
Kostadis Roussos: Something else today.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I mean, I'm… I'm thirsty.
Wade Brown: my soup.
Kostadis Roussos: The soup, the soup is… we could go…
David Mendenhall: Apparently, we have 200 gold pieces.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly, that's a fact.
Wade Brown: by a lot of you.
David Mendenhall: 200 gold.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Not enough, my friend, not enough.
Wade Brown: enough.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I think, I think a little, you know, evening visit to house… What's your name?
Wade Brown: Master.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah?
David Mendenhall: Really?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Should be fun. Yeah, yeah. Then we can go and have dinner.
David Mendenhall: Well, I don't want to meet with those guys.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why not? It'll be fun.
David Mendenhall: They're evil.
Wade Brown: You don't know that yet.
Gary Young: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Bad feeling about them.
David Mendenhall: Ser Kaelen told me to stay away.
Wade Brown: I'll accept that.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't even start.
Gary Young: So what…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What was our business with them?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Other than what, Aurelan just told me.
David Mendenhall: So, so this should, so…
Kostadis Roussos: So usually…
David Mendenhall: But they tried to… they tried to scam…
David Mendenhall: The rightful owner of the brooch Remember?
Kostadis Roussos: The statute.
David Mendenhall: session.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: They ex- they extorted him.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, another… yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so that, the, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So, as you, as you leave the, as you leave the, the,
Kostadis Roussos: So, I presume you're leaving the counting house, yes?
Wade Brown: Yeah, I think we're done here.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
David Mendenhall: Stay with me.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yo, I couldn't find anything about this house.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What's the name?
Kostadis Roussos: what?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: In the quest journal, can't find anything about this house, my gas journal.
David Mendenhall: They are in there…
David Mendenhall: Thought they were in there.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Which one?
David Mendenhall: Elara Seasong Meliamne returns statue from Lighthouse to art collector Neverwinter before House Margaster attacks us.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Where do you see one.
David Mendenhall: of the gauntlet is to thank.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Where do you see it?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, there'.
David Mendenhall: green.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's the green.
David Mendenhall: one.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why is it crossed over, though? Because we returned it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So it's done.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, and then they… they extorted it… extorted money out of her brother.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so what you've discovered about House Margaster is that they've also made an offer to Vukradin as a more efficient redistributor of lost goods.
David Mendenhall: Right, and they made an offer to, Brewbarry.
David Mendenhall: To, increase the profit margins on his business.
Kostadis Roussos: No, they didn't make an offer on Brewbarry. The banker pointed out that they have the cheapest distribution network these days.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, because they're criminals.
Kostadis Roussos: That, that is your interpretation.
David Mendenhall: Well, we witnessed extortion.
Kostadis Roussos: And cool.
David Mendenhall: forgery. We witnessed that.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Though…
Kostadis Roussos: We witnessed it, just as a banker would say, that was one bad apple.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So what's the connection with Linene here and our supply chain?
Kostadis Roussos: So Linene was trying to… so Linene… so what happened was you went to the banker, and Linene was saying, we can arrange it all through Lionshield Coster, right? Yeah. There's… and so the banker being… was trying to be helpful, but Brewbarry didn't want to be helped.
Kostadis Roussos: this was very comedic, by suggesting that House Margaster is a cheaper option, but Brewbarry showed his loyalty to his tribe.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, I was gonna say, sorry for being loyal.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Caribbean stew.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I know, this was conflicting with the Counting House's obsession with profit margins.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right. Yeah, they're only loyal to money. I'm not.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, and so that… and so they were trying to put shit… put… they weren't… they didn't… they don't… he didn't care whether you are or are not gonna work with House Margaster. He's just pointing out that you would get better rates from them.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay, that's a nice story, GM, but you haven't answered my question. What's the connection with Linene's supply chain issue?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so the connection is that… so that you… what you do know is that some time ago.
Kostadis Roussos: the… whatever manifold, the displacement device, you've heard under different names, stopped working, and as a result.
Kostadis Roussos: folks haven't… the Lionshield coster hasn't been able to ship goods the way they used to.
David Mendenhall: So, Brewbarry, let me try to spell it out for you, right? We know that there is this criminal enterprise that is in competition
David Mendenhall: With your preferred distributor, So, a hypothesis is that they sabotaged that competitor.
David Mendenhall: In order to drive more business to them.
Gary Young: And killed… what's her name?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No shit, Sherlock. The question is, what are we gonna do about it?
David Mendenhall: Wow.
Gary Young: time.
David Mendenhall: Do you want to protect your loyal distributor?
Kostadis Roussos: Or do you want to flip, or do you want to flip on and work.
David Mendenhall: Or do you want to help?
Kostadis Roussos: No.
David Mendenhall: Help the ones who stab them in the back.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You really have to ask me this question.
David Mendenhall: Exactly!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Let's get it done before dinner, that's what I said.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're like,
David Mendenhall: You wanna, you wanna attack.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: No, I want to go intimidate them.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Let them know.
Kostadis Roussos: What's cheap.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: They continue to fuck with my business, then they will be fucked.
David Mendenhall: They're not gonna stop just because you told them to stop.
Gary Young: Yeah, they're, they're, they're Cambians.
David Mendenhall: You're gonna have to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm a barbarian, not a thief. You know, I don't work in the shadows.
David Mendenhall: Oh, you don't have to steal.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I let my enemy know that I am there.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And that they will suffer my wrath. That, so let's do that.
David Mendenhall: Okay, what are… we're level 7?
Wade Brown: We're about to be level dead, that's fine. Okay.
Wade Brown: True.
David Mendenhall: Sure. Do you have any, like, magic items, or… Allies…
David Mendenhall: I'm pretty sure they've got, like, the city guard in their pocket, you know, they're gonna call other people to defend. They're gonna have allies, we're not gonna have anybody.
Gary Young: And probably Lord Neverember as well.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, probably the Lord will take their side.
David Mendenhall: We might get expelled from the city.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: As a business profile?
David Mendenhall: UBT.
David Mendenhall: be a thing.
Kostadis Roussos: You won't… the whole… the whole business will fall apart. You will lose the money to build the accounting… to build the business.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Why?
Gary Young: And you won't be able to sell back.
David Mendenhall: You will be banned, and all of your assets seized.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, you know, they do what they do, I'll do what I do.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: They think they can disrupt, you know, my partner's business, so can I.
Wade Brown: He's a barbarian, guys.
David Mendenhall: Maybe we could… I'm gonna…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm just gonna.
David Mendenhall: We could do some stuff, rather than the direct approach, maybe we could do some stabbing in the back.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Weather distribution.
Wade Brown: Network?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm a barbarian, I don't stab in the back. You know, I cut your head while looking at you.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Let me go and make my threats.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And, you know, be the judge of whether or not they are a nuisance, and if I decide that they are, then I'll look into
Stéphane Bourdeaud: How to make them, change their behavior.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Bye.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What do I need to do?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm not a fan.
David Mendenhall: I feel like there's no stopping the man.
Gary Young: Not a fan.
Gary Young: Cope.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You're not a fan?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, very… I think, I think…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: So, just, just to put, put, Brewbarry…
Kostadis Roussos: Even you know impossible odds. But going to intimidate is definitely something you could try to do.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so we'll go with the intimidation. You wanna… you wanna go with the walk-in and…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, yeah, he's an evil, bad guy. He's not gonna help himself, and he's gonna try and rub my nose into it, and give me some serious lead on what I can do to…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, annoying.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Like, if Brewbarry wants to do an intimidation, I will back him up and also try to intimidate. My good friend and best fan.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, so we go knock on House Margaster.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, Olin, before you get there, hold on, before you get there… Before you get there.
Kostadis Roussos: A gentleman approaches himself.
Kostadis Roussos: And,
Kostadis Roussos: introduces himself as Perrin… God, like, why did… why did they pick this name so that I could always be Alagondar.
Kostadis Roussos: So, for those that…
Kostadis Roussos: So, for those of you who recall, the Alagondars were… Lady Alagondar was a high-ranking… was a high-ranking family in Neverwinter. None of you would know this, but the more important point was that she was the grave that had the fireballs.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: She's the owner of the Necklace of Fireballs?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, and
Kostadis Roussos: Ser Kaelen had told you that there was a lead for someone in… when, you know, you wanted to return it to the rightful owners, and the rightful owners, we declared, were,
David Mendenhall: Fire and Blood quest. Return the necklace of Fireballs to Alagondar, the rightful owner.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And so he, he steps back, he's… he's not, he's not, he's, not smooth.
Kostadis Roussos: He's a man in his 30s, and decent but unfashionable clothes, and unfashionable clothes, and he definitely looks like he's been waiting to see… waiting for you guys for a few hours.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, forgive me.
Kostadis Roussos: You're the ones from Phandalin?
Wade Brown: would be…
Kostadis Roussos: Did you say maybe or yes?
Wade Brown: Said we be…
Kostadis Roussos: Okay. I'm sorry, my name is Perrin. Perrin Alagondar. The recovery office wrote to me. They said you'd found…
Kostadis Roussos: And he pauses, very, you know, anxious. He looks very uncomfortable. My family lost something a long time ago. Grave robbers a generation back, we never stopped looking, and they wrote to me last 10 days and said someone had it, and that they were coming here, and I've read the letter about 40 times.
David Mendenhall: Yes, the necklace! We do have it.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks…
David Mendenhall: We have to make sure we're giving it to the right person.
Wade Brown: Can you prove its lineage?
Gary Young: Or at least start with your passport.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, I think that this is absolutely… he goes, yes, I think we should do a proper transfer with all of the paperwork handled in just the right way.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: But not here.
Kostadis Roussos: So does… you asked about proper lineage.
Gary Young: We have a personal banker at the Counting House. We can go there.
David Mendenhall: He's not that good at his job, though.
David Mendenhall: I can't.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes.
Wade Brown: People at least well enough to possibly vet the lineage? I'm not sure.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, so he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: At the mention of the word lineage, but at the mention of the word lineage, he suddenly… you notice a fire in his eye, like something… something clicks, and he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: It goes…
David Mendenhall: The camera zooms in.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, the camera's…
David Mendenhall: Dun dun dun!
David Mendenhall: Very dramatic zoom right then.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, hold on, the camera zooms in.
Wade Brown: And it adds 15 pounds.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, he goes… he starts to explain… he starts to articulate how, you know, that the Alagondars used to be the first family of Neverwinter, and that imposter Neverember, and his lineage has taken the city from them, and imposed,
Wade Brown: We're talking about the necklace here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, no, and he's saying that the necklace is a symbol, a symbol of those who reject the, the… the Neverember line, and that with that symbol, he will be able to rally the forces who oppose his dictatorial high-taxation regime.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: yawn very loudly.
David Mendenhall: It's just an.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: necklace, do you…
David Mendenhall: me you're going to start a revolution with the next one?
Wade Brown: I don't know if I want that on my hands.
Kostadis Roussos: And he goes, no, I'm not going to start a revolution, no, no, this is a symbol, I'm not about the revolution, this is just a symbol.
David Mendenhall: Well, it's your necklace. Assuming you can, you know… Establish your identity, etc, etc.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I mean, if this necklace is the symbol that you say it is, I'd imagine a lot of people would lie to claim it's theirs.
David Mendenhall: Sounds… yeah, that's a good point.
David Mendenhall: Well said.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Then, just so, so, so,
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, so just as he's standing there, you notice somebody step out of the shadows.
Kostadis Roussos: I'll not step out of the shadows. You've noticed him for some moment.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: How many people are gonna get in our path?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I was…
Kostadis Roussos: You guys are, like, a little bit… I mean, just to be clear, you guys have become somewhat of a local legend, right? This is what happens when you get between.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Maybe we should have office hours, you know, and people can get a ticket.
David Mendenhall: What we get for just trouncing around without bodyguards, without… Without sunglasses, the paparazzi.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I…
David Mendenhall: following you.
Gary Young: I'll be sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: See the tag, let's
Kostadis Roussos: But let's just be clear. We have a 6-foot-something guy who looks like Goliath, dressed in… What do you mean?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: looks like I am the Goli.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: You know?
Wade Brown: He's got, like, a 30-foot reach. He's a Goliath.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right. And we've got… we've got a turtle, and we've got, with the staff of Meril, and we've got a drow cleric of Lathander whose eyes glow with the blessing of Lathander. You're not exactly inconspicuous.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, but I mean, this isn't Houston, Texas. This is Neverwinter in the Forgotten Realms. We can't be the only party looking like this.
Wade Brown: Yeah, there's.
Kostadis Roussos: No, but you're the… But you guys are the new guys.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: The fashions…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: What does this guy emerging from the shadows want?
Kostadis Roussos: He produces a paper.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of course he does.
David Mendenhall: He says that he's the rightful owner of the necklace.
Kostadis Roussos: How many feet.
David Mendenhall: And that it belongs to… dun dun dun, House Margaster!
Wade Brown: Please don't be.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, he does… no, that's actually not what happens.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown: Which part? The House Margaster, or the, paper is produced?
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Wade Brown: Or both.
Wade Brown: Sorry, Margaster, I keep…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he produces a piece of paper, that, yes, once again, is sealed with the paperwork of House Margaster, proving that Perrin Alagondar is, in fact, the rightful owner of said necklace of fireballs.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
Wade Brown: I mean, either he just walks around with this, or…
David Mendenhall: is the one vouching for Alagondar. Well, that's a twist.
Kostadis Roussos: And so he produces the paper and says.
Kostadis Roussos: and suggest that, you know, that everything is copacetic, everything is completely above board, but if they really… if you really, really insist on making a fuss over this, we could always head over to House Margaster at our official offices, where we can present to you the full lineage.
Wade Brown: I mean, Brewbarry wants to go to the house, right?
David Mendenhall: I wanted to go there anyway, but if you intimidate them.
Wade Brown: I'm… I'm okay with… I'm okay with conjoining these objectives.
David Mendenhall: We might have to sequence them, though. We might need to…
David Mendenhall: Handle the necklace, and then do the intimidation.
Wade Brown: That's… I think that's fine. I mean, it's still one trip.
Wade Brown: Honestly, I cut it.
David Mendenhall: I don't know, but Rueberg's gonna go straight for the intimidation.
Wade Brown: Well, I'm okay with him doing it first.
Wade Brown: And as a result, we'll see what happens with the necklace, I mean…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly, maybe we can use it as leverage.
Wade Brown: Or we can use it.
David Mendenhall: It's not…
Kostadis Roussos: The, the fixer, the fixer… The guy, the guy…
Wade Brown: away.
Kostadis Roussos: The guy, the House Margaster guy says, pauses and says, You know.
Kostadis Roussos: And he looks at his… he looks at the time and says, it's gonna be late, I… could we just not just do this right here? I give you the… here, this is an official piece of paper.
David Mendenhall: So let's head over. You know, we've got time. Day's not over.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, the opposite… the opposite.
David Mendenhall: We were headed there anyway. Yeah, why don't you come with us?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Well.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And I grab him by the neck, and I say, no, you're coming.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I think you'll definitely be coming with us.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright, show the way.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're grabbing a…
Wade Brown: Scruffing him, like.
David Mendenhall: It's not a kidnapping!
Wade Brown: Taking him home.
David Mendenhall: I want to be clear, we're just… we're just, you know… supporting him.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly.
David Mendenhall: We don't want them to fall down.
Kostadis Roussos: At this point in time, Boney opens his mouth.
Wade Brown: Pony!
David Mendenhall: Boney? Where the hell is that.
Kostadis Roussos: Don't forget, Boney was Lady Alagondar's… No, she's been in the city with you guys, you're outside, you're outside. Canonically, you're outside, right?
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: This is fine, he's with us.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he's with us, and Boney, at this point in time, adopts a huffing and puffing kind of pose. I mean, as much as a skeletal.
Wade Brown: With no lungs or anything, like…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And looks at him and says, and says, you are a member of the Alagondars?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, yeah, and he goes, and who exactly did this necklace belong to?
Kostadis Roussos: Right? Because Boney obviously knows exactly who the necklace belonged to, and the lineage, and whatnot. Because, you know… and so…
Wade Brown: from the Alagondars.
Kostadis Roussos: Bud?
Wade Brown: Get it going?
Kostadis Roussos: And… It's quite clear… You can see…
Kostadis Roussos: He goes… the Perrin looks at him, he goes,
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he goes, well, it was… see, you know, I can't really… well, it was, he, he, you immediately get the sense that he's… doesn't quite know
Kostadis Roussos: all of the facts. On top of which, Boney knows the fact that the necklace wasn't stolen until very recently, when a certain Vukradin decided to return it, and so Perrin's story has some holes in it.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: You get them, Boney.
Kostadis Roussos: So Boney is, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Boney is very skeptical about the authenticity of this Alagondar's claim to, being the rightful owner of said necklace, and is very dubious about the claims about how it got lost and whatnot.
Wade Brown: And that makes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, let's find out if this paper really comes from House Margaster, and if they say that it does, then let's use Boney as a witness to expose them as frauds. I'm sure.
David Mendenhall: Oh, that'll hold up in court. A skeletal horse.
Wade Brown: Sure.
Wade Brown: That doesn't mean it's any kind of legit.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, alright, okay, okay. I just wanted you to know that there, that the Boney… Boney does, you know, Boney does express, but then Boney then goes, says, but I have been dead for some time.
Wade Brown: Not bad, Lol.
Kostadis Roussos: We can pauses.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, dead as a relative term, I mean, I was a bony creature.
Wade Brown: Oh, pony.
Gary Young: I probably don't think that Boney is of the goodly racist.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I prefer the term, recently unalived.
Wade Brown: Yeah, Boney's a Zoomer.
David Mendenhall: Terrible.
Kostadis Roussos: Good.
David Mendenhall: normal.
Wade Brown: Algorithm has saved him from ban… From demonetization.
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: Exactly.
Wade Brown: Unalived is used to avoid demonetization, that's all.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, I know, that's why I started laughing. It took me a second to catch up with you, man.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So does somebody else emerge from the shadows, or are we.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, that's it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: 22 House Margaster, okay.
Wade Brown: Nobody else claiming lineage or, ownership here?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, nobody else is claiming lineage.
Kostadis Roussos: Paradise…
Wade Brown: But it's… anyway.
Kostadis Roussos: Perrin, though, you know, after Boney makes his accusations, insists that he has all the paperwork necessary, and will produce it on, if necessary, and that his agent, points to the fixer, has already provide… can provide that information as well, but they have to… you'd have to go to the notary
Kostadis Roussos: To, to get that information.
David Mendenhall: Everybody works with them are casters.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, you can have as many papers as you want. If Bonnie says you're not kosher, then you're not kosher.
Kostadis Roussos: Boney pauses and says, Mr. Brewbarry… no, he goes, Brewbarry, Brewbarry, Brewbarry Bird. I simply can point out that there are holes in the story. I can't really say whether he is or is not. I did not… I… as you know, I was… spent some time in a tomb.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, Boney, do you know who the necklace belongs to? Yes or no?
Kostadis Roussos: I belong to Lady Alagondar, and if he indeed is a member of the Alagondar clan, it is entirely possible that he has a rightful claim to it. And therefore, and all of a sudden, you realize that Boney, among many of his other unbelievably cute traits, is a… is a… obsessed about lineages and parents, and, like, grandparents, and.
Wade Brown: No, he's falling.
Wade Brown: Follows the royal families, as it were.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, he follows the royal family, who's born to whom, you know, what the rights of succession are.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, if you're stuck in a tomb for a few hundred years, you start to, like, do research.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Wade Brown: Is that… do we…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Makes sense.
Wade Brown: There were records in there, like, new ones?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, there was a few. I mean, you're also… yes, there was a few.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it was a tomb, right?
Wade Brown: Yeah, oh, riot, new… new corpses.
Wade Brown: The records were… yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: There were corpses, it was a tomb, so that's how you studied it.
Wade Brown: I… I'm slow.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I understand the motivation, you have to explain to me the logistics of it. I don't know how Boney horse can do some research in books and stuff.
Wade Brown: He's not doing bad on books, he's doing it on the gravestones themselves.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay. Yes.
Wade Brown: So you could see, like, you know, here lies X, you know, married to Y…
Wade Brown: Yes. I realize Lady Alagondar married to Pengro, you know, whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright. Okay, so what… so you have a couple of choices. We can take… you can take the knight and go back, or you want to go head straight to House Margaster.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: straight.
David Mendenhall: We've got our friends with us.
Wade Brown: Yeah, we're dragging him along.
Gary Young: In the evening, at night, maybe? I mean, that's fantastic. Good plan.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, exactly.
David Mendenhall: a concert.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Let's go.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Wade Brown: Hmm, hmm, excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: bridge.
Wade Brown: Oh.
Gary Young: Stephane?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes?
Gary Young: Add to your character elven chain mail.
Gary Young: Because we might end up in some combat here.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: To my character, what?
Gary Young: Elven chainmail.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Elven chain mail.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay. Yeah. And that…
Gary Young: Places for a scale mail.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Manage inventory… Items… Elven… chain mail…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, you arrive at…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: to equipment…
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so, you arrive all… the guy who's with Perrin.
Kostadis Roussos: is, you know, kind of says, well, if we're gonna go get this, let's go get it done properly. And so he, he kind of, like.
Kostadis Roussos: Tries to get you to stop holding him.
Kostadis Roussos: Dude.
David Mendenhall: I'm sure a brewery.
Wade Brown: Grips is nice and gentle.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It tries to. Try is the key word here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Try.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he, he, after trying for a few moments, he just gives up.
Kostadis Roussos: Meanwhile, you know, the fact that you're dressed like Brewbarry and acting like a barbarian is, like, not causing anybody, like, but, you know, there's a bunch of Brewbarry lookalikes who are, like, really impressed with your commitment to the bit.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Good to know.
Kostadis Roussos: Good movie.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: This, as they say on Mandalore, this is the way.
David Mendenhall: Work.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: You arrive at a notary house.
David Mendenhall: Going to the Marcasters.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: it… the…
Wade Brown: I know he said we could do that, but we're just dragging him back home to get the paperwork, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, right. And, well, so it turns out that the… so, as you walk in, he explains that this notary house belongs to the Margasters.
David Mendenhall: no shit.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: What doesn't? What don't they control?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, many.
Wade Brown: That's why it's easier in the forest, guys, none of this crap.
David Mendenhall: Control the order of the gauntlet.
Kostadis Roussos: No, they don't… they don't.
Kostadis Roussos: They will soon.
David Mendenhall: Well, I'm sure they're trying.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: SystemD of Neverwinter.
David Mendenhall: So, I'd like to look around, do I see anything, like…
David Mendenhall: obviously… I guess not obviously, or subtly amiss, signs of criminal activity, forgery, deception.
Wade Brown: A meth lab just out in the open.
David Mendenhall: you know, 13 investigations. Maybe Gary could look, too?
Gary Young: How about a…
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Gary Young: 20 insights, and then…
Gary Young: 20… Wait, what? I think double rolls.
David Mendenhall: You got a 9 perception?
Gary Young: Looks like I had a 9 perception.
David Mendenhall: We're going with the Insight roll.
Gary Young: 2018.
David Mendenhall: Anybody else want to look around?
Wade Brown: Oh, sure.
David Mendenhall: The notary?
Wade Brown: It's… Come on, did that roll? Where's the…
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so,
Kostadis Roussos: It is, in fact, just a notary. It doesn't have any of the usual, you know.
Kostadis Roussos: Margaster, you know, demonic…
David Mendenhall: So, all the forgeries happen off-site, and they just.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: They're just notarized here.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but…
Gary Young: They notarized forgeries. Got it.
David Mendenhall: This is not, this is not Forgery Central.
Wade Brown: They make the paperwork to legitimize their… business ventures.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, so you arrive at the notary.
Kostadis Roussos: And the notary… the notary is very pleased to see you.
Kostadis Roussos: He, he asks you to sit down, and he, he says, so, how can I be of assistance? Perrin explains.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the… the family of, this, this, the, the, he points to you guys, have brought an artifact that belongs to me and has been notarized, and… and the other guy shows the paperwork that demonstrates the notarization.
Kostadis Roussos: And, Perrin says, with, with this official document, the, the, the necklace, the heirloom that belonged to my family, the symbol of the true, rightful heirs of…
Kostadis Roussos: of Neverwinter, will be recognized.
David Mendenhall: But how do we know that this is the gentleman who says he is? I mean, anybody can impersonate anybody. He could be a polymorph, for all we know.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Disguise self as…
Kostadis Roussos: So, so, the, the, the, the, the… the, what's his name?
Kostadis Roussos: the, the, the… The notary. The notary.
Kostadis Roussos: Sorry, I'm trying to keep all these characters in my head in my head.
Kostadis Roussos: the notary.
Kostadis Roussos: says, well, it's quite clear here, right? And he shows you… he pulls out the book, which is titled Genealogy of the Alagondars.
Kostadis Roussos: And, he says this was verified with the usual procedures against forgeries, doppelgangers, miscellaneous magic using the threefold rule.
Kostadis Roussos: of coordinating between three different sources of conflicting evidence with different provenance, and you can clearly see that Perrin Alagondar is, in fact, a descendant, a rightful descendant, of Lady Alagondar, and that if this is indeed stolen goods, as,
Kostadis Roussos: As he claims, he absolutely deserves to have it back.
David Mendenhall: No, I got that, I agree. But how do I know he's Perrin Alagondar?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, oh, well, I mean…
Wade Brown: He looks like a paragraph, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, like, how do we… well, he goes, the house… he goes, oh, well, if that is your concern, I think that is utterly a reasonable concern, at which point.
Kostadis Roussos: the guy who holds the paperwork. Well, we have… there's a very simple solution, Mr. Vukradin, and this is a very common problem that we've seen with many folks in Neverwinter, when they're making these kinds of deals. And this is, by the way.
Kostadis Roussos: And why…
Wade Brown: Deal.
Kostadis Roussos: This is why House Margaster acts as the honest broker on the return of such goods.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So we're supposed to take your word for it.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no. He was… he's actually…
David Mendenhall: You don't have to take his word.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Are you calling me a liar?
Gary Young: We're taking Margesser's word for it.
David Mendenhall: It's title insurance!
Wade Brown: Awww.
David Mendenhall: That's all it is, it's title insurance!
Wade Brown: How can I lose?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's what we were wearing called bulls.
David Mendenhall: We can't really guarantee anything, but if it's wrong, we'll take care of you.
Kostadis Roussos: So, actually, he's very confused about this. It was told Title Insurance, but you can see his eyes, you know, clicking, going, hmm, this might be an interesting scam we could pull in the future.
David Mendenhall: charge thousands of dollars, they'll never even know! They'll just sign it because, hey, who cares?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't sure.
Wade Brown: Can they also give an extended warranty on this necklace? As long as we're here?
David Mendenhall: Excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: So…
Kostadis Roussos: The notary says, all these flavors of insurance are, I'm sure, are… could definitely be products that could be offered in the future, but in the present, what we could do is we could, give, keep the necklace in layaway in House Margaster's warehouses.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Not happening. Alright, until you can produce 3 independent, independent from housemaghaster, witnesses as to who you really are.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: and it proves to us that it is… you are who you say you are, then, you know, you can take a walk and forget about the necklace. Thank you very much. Now, on to our other business.
David Mendenhall: our casters. Brewbarry. We're gonna remember the intimidation?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, we're going to the Marcasters.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: Right, so the easiest way to go to the bargasters is to give the necklace.
David Mendenhall: You can just walk there.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, you're gonna walk there? Alright. So, you're telling Perrin he's not getting the necklace, and you're telling the other guy he's not getting the necklace?
David Mendenhall: No, but they're coming with us.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: We want to settle this at the source.
David Mendenhall: The notary could come, too, if he'd like.
David Mendenhall: The more allies our casters have, the better for us.
Kostadis Roussos: We need to…
Wade Brown: We need you to have more characters to track.
David Mendenhall: And more enemies for us to fight.
Gary Young: Comments…
Kostadis Roussos: What am I?
Wade Brown: easy.
Gary Young: You know, we have yet to take over the Spire of the Morninglord to have more allies, just noting that.
David Mendenhall: Actually, that would be… maybe we should recruit some more allies. This is gonna be a pretty… this battle's gonna be pretty one-sided.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We're just gonna threaten the crime laws.
David Mendenhall: Oh, right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: down, you know, and then we can take care of…
David Mendenhall: And then we're fleeing, yep.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes. You know.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so as you're heading past, as you're heading towards… the House Margaster.
Kostadis Roussos: You canonically, of course, because in city adventures, players can go any which way they want, so the GM has to simply declare, you pass by.
Kostadis Roussos: I have learned this over the last 2 years.
Kostadis Roussos: You pass by a building,
Kostadis Roussos: As you're headed towards the,
Kostadis Roussos: headed towards House Margasters, a business establishment near the docks, a dead displacement
Kostadis Roussos: A building that looks shut down. And as you notice it, there's a civic notice nailed to the door.
Wade Brown: It's on the notice.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: In order to sake.
Kostadis Roussos: It says, displacement… no, it declares…
Kostadis Roussos: that the… that this building has been shut down till further notice, by order of Lord Neverember.
Kostadis Roussos: And that the services provided by the dis… the services provided for instantaneous shipping have been closed until further.
Wade Brown: Oh, that's…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so you get the impression that this is perhaps where the manifold was housed.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay, does this Perrin guy know anything about this? Why, why did they close down this establishment? This fine establishment, I might add.
Kostadis Roussos: Lucrative establishment.
Kostadis Roussos: Who are you asking? Perrin? No, Perrin has no clue.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, oh, Perrin… Perrin simply says that the… the… the… it stopped working. Nobody knows quite why it stopped working.
Kostadis Roussos: And that this… and then he pauses and says that this is probably… he goes on some revolutionary tirade about how the Neverwinter Commission has its hands in everything.
Kostadis Roussos: And controls everything. And because it controls everything, they probably shut it down so they can… so that the cheap and easy way to ship goods would be turned into a mechanism of control, etc.
Wade Brown: How convenient for House Margaster, isn't it?
Gary Young: You said the Neverwinter Commission.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Haven't we been invited by Lord Neverwinter to have dinner?
David Mendenhall: That paid us for the mine?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Great.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'm starting to see your point.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: What? What?
Wade Brown: They have… they wield their influence, flagrantly.
Kostadis Roussos: The Neverwinter Commission, you could ask about the Neverwinter Commission, but we can keep going. Alright.
Gary Young: I happen to think that undermining power structures is best done behind the scenes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Very well. Alright.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it would be guided if they don't know that we're doing this.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: It's not so firmly, no.
Gary Young: Just, like, they don't need evidence that… But they don't.
Wade Brown: They don't need evidence or a reason to disappear anyone.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Well, they gotta know who it is, otherwise that person doesn't have any leverage. You know, you let them know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Not make it obvious.
Wade Brown: I love having blueberries.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Then you sabotage, then they know where it's coming from, and then, you know, they're forced to sit at the table.
Wade Brown: I truly love you, man, this is fantastic.
Kostadis Roussos: This is, this is awesome, like, this is great.
Wade Brown: No, I love it. I'm totally here for you.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so you're at the Margasters Logistic Operations Eastern Quay.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you're dragging, you know, I guess at this point in time, Perrin…
Wade Brown: Marin, and…
Kostadis Roussos: The notary hasn't… unless the notary did not come with you.
Wade Brown: Alright.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: As you, the operation looks… it looks like it's a well-run operation. There's, why don't we, roll some insight or investigation checks?
Wade Brown: Let's see if I can't flub this one…
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, I think,
Wade Brown: Oh, wow, even worse.
Kostadis Roussos: What did you get, Gary? Sorry, I don't have my roll 20 up right now.
Gary Young: Only 21.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, well, so, fine. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Soma… Soma notices that it's clean.
Wade Brown: Well kept.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so very, very, very impressively cleaned and organized. On the other hand, Valphine, who's,
Kostadis Roussos: Family was involved in all sorts of
Kostadis Roussos: Shall we refer to it as trade?
Kostadis Roussos: goods, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Is able to quickly diagn… is able to quickly see that this place is an extremely well… run operations.
Kostadis Roussos: And, she notices that there's all sorts of Lionshield labeled goods.
Kostadis Roussos: In boxes.
Gary Young: Oh, Lionshield.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Lionshield Coster Goods.
Kostadis Roussos: That clearly House Margaster… right, so House Margaster…
Gary Young: else who are guest hers.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Gary Young: I suppose.
Kostadis Roussos: So essentially, how House Margaster is now moving… so LionShield didn't have a move… didn't have a transportation service, because they relied on their displacement device, so now they're being forced to pay money to have the goods moved.
Gary Young: to Margaster.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, through Margaster. Margaster's not interested in possessing the goods. Margaster's interested in…
Wade Brown: They're sweating their beak, yeah, they just want the profits.
Kostadis Roussos: They're just… so yeah, so they're definitely in the business of moving goods, not stealing goods.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, at least this part… this part of the operation.
Gary Young: This particular apparatus is, yeah.
Wade Brown: It's a legitimate business front.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Wade Brown: They are legitimately moving goods, how they're getting all the business is lessened legitimate.
Gary Young: And how exactly are they moving the goods?
Wade Brown: Oh, that's.
Kostadis Roussos: God.
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know…
Gary Young: Not through displacement, by any chance.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, that, you know, the usual caravans with armed guards, the usual thing.
Gary Young: Huh.
Wade Brown: Old school.
Gary Young: It sounds like a very expensive way to move guts.
Kostadis Roussos: and profitable.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: They're the only game in town. They can charge whatever they want, no matter how expensive it is.
Gary Young: Hmm…
Kostadis Roussos: Again… All right, so, again, and then your favorite guy, Cullen Sharpe, walks up.
David Mendenhall: Who's called?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, insurance.
Kostadis Roussos: He's the guy who was in the green suit.
Kostadis Roussos: Who showed up at… he's the guy who made the deal with, what's the Lord.
David Mendenhall: Now you tried… who extorted…
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: This asshole. Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Lord Cassian, so Cullen Sharpe is very happy to see you.
Kostadis Roussos: And, and is very excited.
Kostadis Roussos: And says…
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, he's, you know, he's kind of a smooth, you know… he's a smooth guy, he's not a, you know…
Wade Brown: Sure.
David Mendenhall: He's working on commission.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, he's not, he's not, he's…
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, roll your, your insight.
Gary Young: Hold on, just a second. Let me test something.
Gary Young: Okay, that's what it was. Insight.
Kostadis Roussos: What is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Totally.
David Mendenhall: insight.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so…
Gary Young: You beat me.
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, I think you have a special ability now related to your character, where you can detect lies or cause people who are lying.
Gary Young: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm surprised you hadn't… just wanted to remind you of it.
Gary Young: Thank you.
Wade Brown: That's true.
Gary Young: where is that ability?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of course, is lying, he's a thug.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, so he says there, he goes, so he's very excited to see you, And he goes.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr. Vukradin, I'm so delighted to see you. Oh, and Mr. Perrin, I hope everything is going… that the letter of introduction we provided was sufficient, the evidence, and then he turns to you and says, Mr. Vukradin, I wish, I hope you see from how we manage that we are very good at solving one of the problems.
Kostadis Roussos: that Ser Kaelen suggested you might have when he reached out to us through one of our agents, that perhaps we could provide the connecting tissue between your fines and the real proprietaires using our, you know, patented system.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That is what we're here for.
David Mendenhall: So, Brewbarry, let's do some intimidation.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That's what we're here for, my good man, solving problems and getting your help into solving problems.
David Mendenhall: What'd you get, Brewbarry?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Intimidation, let me roll it.
Wade Brown: Hmm.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, goddamn. Alright.
David Mendenhall: Alright, a 6, awesome.
Wade Brown: Vukradin.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Whoa.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Do the joke!
David Mendenhall: Oh, man, you chose.
Wade Brown: The robe, man, the robe just makes you look so soft and, you know…
David Mendenhall: That's why I.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So…
David Mendenhall: Back you up. 15.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, Colin, my good friend, I tap, I, you know, pat him on the back, you're gonna help us solve problems, do exactly what you said you would do.
Kostadis Roussos: First of all, so let's just be clear. Let's just be clear. He's not intimidated, but he's appreciating, he's appreciating.
David Mendenhall: He's amused. He's amused by the situation.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I have a good friend of mine, a, you know, you might call it a business partner, who has this shipping company that was using this,
Stéphane Bourdeaud: device that suddenly, you know… broke. Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: And the house was shut down, and then they have to rely now on your fine establishment to transport their goods. I was wondering if you could, you know, enlighten me as to what exactly happened to this device. Maybe you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Don't you? And I firm my grip on his shoulder.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see, does he…
Kostadis Roussos: I have to… I have to remember what… how… what I said. This is…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You know, Colin, I've been told that you're quite sharp, no pun intended.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So you said his name was Cullen Sharpe.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Colin.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So surely you know something about this?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: See, so he… well, what he says is that…
Kostadis Roussos: He, he, so you, you failed your intimidation check, so…
Kostadis Roussos: he's not intimidated by you, but he simply points as, my dear friend, Mr. Brewbarry, can I call your friend?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of course, of course, we are. Frontier.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, we're all friends. So, my friend Brewbarry. The device you're referring to is, was run by, House,
Kostadis Roussos: House,
Wade Brown: That was nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: was not run by House Margaster. We were not involved with the operation of that thing, and perhaps if we had been, it would not have gotten damaged and been no longer operable. To be honest with you, I don't think I know what happened, although I do know that there was some
Kostadis Roussos: Gnome that was hired to attempt to fix it, and as a result of the attempts to fix it, or was it to improve its operation, it stopped working.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I mean, might you have the name of this?
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Gnome.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm sorry, I wouldn't have…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Truly, a man of your, you know, knowledge.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you know.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: influence.
Kostadis Roussos: See, perhaps if you were to come tomorrow, or we were to resolve some… we were to enter into a business arrangement, I would be more inclined to see if…
David Mendenhall: Event persuasion. Does that help?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Mr. Vukra did. Mr. Vukra did. I, I, I think… you know.
Kostadis Roussos: I'd love to help. In fact, I will help. But I… I don't have the informa… I don't… I personally don't have the information. I'll have to ask around, so if you're willing to come tomorrow, I will… I will give it to you. But can we… can we go back to…
David Mendenhall: We've got a lot going on tomorrow, so we've got a concert. Do you think you guys could come to the concert.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, absolutely!
David Mendenhall: Yeah, because we're… it's a benefit.
David Mendenhall: It's a benefit, and, and
David Mendenhall: We really want lots of people to come and donate to this important cause.
David Mendenhall: Do you think you could get, like, the whole house to come?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't… I don't think I could do that, but I'm certain I, as a representative of the House, would be more than delighted to show up.
Gary Young: That would be excellent.
David Mendenhall: Well, better than nobody.
Wade Brown: Something, yeah.
Gary Young: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: He may not be the only person to show up, but I'm just…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Male also suggests that, you know, you may see this as a business opportunity. I mean, should we get this device working again? And, you know, I've heard it's quite brilliant at transporting goods at a very cheap rate. This could be a business opportunity.
David Mendenhall: We're not doing any business with it.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of course we're not, but it doesn't… it doesn't hurt to suggest it.
David Mendenhall: But you're deceiving them. Is that what's going on, Brewbarry? Sidebar?
David Mendenhall: Okay, got it.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll your… roll your deception, bro.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Oh, god damn it. Why do we have to roll dice all the time?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'm just…
David Mendenhall: How about a 1? Come on, one!
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I roll poly.
David Mendenhall: 11.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Houle.
David Mendenhall: You got two ones.
Kostadis Roussos: manage it.
Kostadis Roussos: He doesn't notice… he doesn't notice the lie. He thinks you're just being a barbarian who doesn't know what he's talking about.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Exactly. Perfect cover, and I don't…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, like…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Good. By the way?
David Mendenhall: We'll take that, we'll take that.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, guys.
David Mendenhall: I gotta go to bed.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, you find out who the gnome is for me, you find out exactly what happened.
David Mendenhall: I have a feeling.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Pretty nice.
David Mendenhall: Know who the gnome is.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Because, you know, machines get broke, or supply chains get disrupted, things happen.
Wade Brown: Right, right.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, just so we're on the same page.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Next, go…
Kostadis Roussos: The parent and the parent and the fixer are… the parent and the guy with the paperwork are still there, and they want their… the necklace of fireballs, so you…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: They know what they gotta do, produce 3 independent witnesses that can guarantee who he is.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so that's what you want. Alright, so… and how House Margaster is suggesting that you can hand over the necklace of fireballs to them for safekeeping, and you've decided not to go down that route.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, why would we need to do that? We brought it all this way.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, there…
Stéphane Bourdeaud: We are the…
Gary Young: Play safe.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Of the necklace. Yeah. Not how smart, yeah.
David Mendenhall: It's much safer with us.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes. Right.
Kostadis Roussos: You do notice…
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, the guy who's got the… who produced the paperwork looks a little bit, unhappy.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yeah, I take the paperwork, I make a little paper ball with it, and then I toss it over my shoulder. It's like…
David Mendenhall: You're always egging them on, man.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Is that making it crystal clear for you, Perry?
Kostadis Roussos: I just… yeah.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Whoever you are.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, Mr. Speaker, just to be clear.
David Mendenhall: nation.
Kostadis Roussos: The guy, the guy with the paper, the guy with the paper, it's momentarily.
Kostadis Roussos: pretend… momentarily thinks to reach for his weapon, and Colin looks at him, and he doesn't.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Right.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Wise decision.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Now, don't make me…
Kostadis Roussos: So there'.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: You eat that paper, that piece of paper, and, you know, chop, chop, move along.
Kostadis Roussos: Mr. Sharp says, Mr, the gentlemen… the gentlemen are sticklers for ritual and control in how Margaster's business is to make sure that the customer is satisfied, and we will provide all the information.
Kostadis Roussos: You need a parent…
Gary Young: I would like to rule a 24 perception on the, on the paperwork.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay, so the paperwork, I mean, to the… so…
Wade Brown: So much for going to bed, Dave?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no, let me… no, no, let me answer that. The paperwork… so you do look at the paperwork, and it is, in fact.
Kostadis Roussos: What you perceive from the paperwork is that it is authentic, alright?
Kostadis Roussos: And that… and that it does have the correct sets of information. It's not like Perrin was lying.
David Mendenhall: I mean, so he's not a cheap fraud. Alagondar has allied with Margaster.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: be.
David Mendenhall: Right? And they're trying to, together, overthrow… Lord Neverwinter, something like that. Right. Could all be totally legitimate, and they're still evil.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, just to be clear, it's… the paperwork is clear, like, it doesn't…
David Mendenhall: Yeah, this is really…
Gary Young: I mean, I was looking for a…
David Mendenhall: is if we can establish his identity, and he's the rightful owner of the necklace, we have to turn over the necklace. If he then takes the necklace, puts it on, and shoots a fireball at us, well, that sucks, but that's what we have to do anyway.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright.
Kostadis Roussos: So just to be clear, the paperwork is clear. I just want to be clear, the paperwork is clean.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Yes, but what's not clean is we don't know if he is who he says he is.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I mean, yeah, I mean, he… so, yeah, so he… he will… he has stuff at his house that he's happy to provide for you.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: That stuff, we want witnesses, and witnesses that aren't in House Margaster's pocket.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, that… that he can provide that too.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: I'll provide that, and then you'll get what you do.
Kostadis Roussos: And he suggests, and he suggests an inn that you guys can all meet at, where he will provide all of that information.
David Mendenhall: I thought we were gonna meet at, House Margaster.
Kostadis Roussos: No, you are in House Margaster.
Gary Young: We're gonna meet at the Church of Lathander after the sermon.
Kostadis Roussos: After the servant. Is that where you want to meet with… that's where you want to meet with Perrin?
Gary Young: Yes.
David Mendenhall: We'll be doing…
Gary Young: I definitely want to see him.
David Mendenhall: gig.
David Mendenhall: And we have to tell the whole town the new name of the band.
Kostadis Roussos: All right. Okay, so, so, so, you tell Perrin we'll meet after the church service at the Spire of the Morninglord, is that what I'm hearing?
Gary Young: Yes, I definitely want to see him set foot within the temple.
Kostadis Roussos: Hurry.
David Mendenhall: Nice. Interesting task.
David Mendenhall: Alright, I like that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay, so Perrin is very happy to do that. He explains that he, too, is a… although not a exclusive worshipper of the Morninglord, is a big believer in the morning lords, and he starts talking about the, you know, mourning Lord as a god of good, etc, etc, etc.
Kostadis Roussos: Valdide, do you roll your eyes, or do you keep your smile straight and just smile more teethily, or just are completely blase?
Gary Young: Just blase.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So, so I'm… I missed something before we conclude this. There was this other guy who was pretending that he owned the necklace. Who was he again? Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it wasn't… he doesn't… he… he's an agent of… he's an agent of House Margaster.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: He was also an agent of House Margaster, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yeah, you're…
Wade Brown: Everyone in town is.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: So we need to find out, next session, we need to find out.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: who is not with House Margaster, and we need to align with those people, just in case, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Alright, guys.
Stéphane Bourdeaud: Alright.